Guide to the Richard Kelly Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project files, 1939-1977; Series I
  - John Hancock Center. (Gen. Motors Technical Ctr.), 1952
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 32)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 32)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 32)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 32)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 32)
  - Johnson, Philip
    - Unidentified Material (Box 359)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 359)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 399)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 404)
  - Johnson, Philip Office Building
    - Unidentified Material (Box 359)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 359)
    - Photographs (Box 34)
  - Johnson, Philip Guest House
    - Unidentified Material (Box 359)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 359)
    - Drawings (Box 359)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 359)
  - Junior Formals Inc., 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 32)
    - Drawings (Box 32)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 32)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 32)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 32)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 32)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 32)
  - Junior Sophisticates Company Showroom, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 32)
  - Jurka, Dr. Edith House, 1966-1967
    Job location: Croton on Hudson, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 32, Box 404)
    - Drawings (Box 32, Box 337)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 404)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 32, Box 337)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 32, Box 404)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 32, Box 404)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 32)
  - Kaiser, Edgar Apartment, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 33)
    - Drawings (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 33)
  - Kaiser, Edgar Office, 1953
    Job location: Oakland, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 33)
    - Drawings (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 33)
  - Kaiser, Henry Apartment, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 33)
    - Drawings (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 33)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 33)
  - Kaiser, Henry Company, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 33)
    - Drawings (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 33)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 33)
  - Kaiser, Henry Residence, 1951
    Job location: Happy Valley, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 33)
    - Drawings (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 33)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 33)
  - Kaiser, Henry Residence
    Job location: Lake Tahoe, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 33)
    - Drawings (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 33)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 33)
    - Photographs (Box 33)
  - Kaiser Permanente Hospital, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 33)
    - Drawings (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 33)
  - Kaufman, Edgar Sr. Residence
    Job location: Palm Springs, CA
    Collaborator: Richard Neutra
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 33)
    - Drawings (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 33)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 33)
  - Kaufman, Edgar Sr. Apartment, 1953
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 33)
  - Kaufman, Edgar Jr. Apartment
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 33)
    - Drawings (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 33)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 33)
    - Photographs (Box 33)
  - Kellogg, Francis Residence, 1948
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 33)
    - Drawings (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 33)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 33)
  - Kelly, Richard Apartment, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 33, Box 404, Box 412)
    - Drawings (Box 33, Box 404)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 401)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 401)
    - Photographs (Box 404)
  - Kelly, Richard Bridgeport Building, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 33)
    - Drawings (Box 33)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 33)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 33)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 33)
  - Kelly, Richard Job Index and Bibliography, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 34)
  - Kelly, Richard Light Index, 1960-1969
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 34)
    - Drawings (Box 34)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 34)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 34)
  - Kelly, Richard Offices (See also: Union Carbide and Carbon Corporation Building), 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 34, Box 404)
    - Drawings (Box 34, Box 404)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 34)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 34)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 34)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 34, Box 385)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 34)
  - Kelly, Richard Oyster House, 1949
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 34)
    - Drawings (Box 34)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 34)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 34)
  - Kelly, Richard Residence, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 34)
    - Drawings (Box 34)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 34)
  - Kenin, Abel, 1953
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 34)
    - Drawings (Box 34)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 34)
  - Kent Lighting Corporation, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 34)
    - Drawings (Box 34)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 34)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 34)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 34)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 34)
  - Kimbell Art Museum, 1970
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 93A, Box 405)
    - Drawings (Box 93, Box 97–99, Box 102, Box 113–114)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 93, Box 102, Box 405)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 94, Box 102, Box 113–114)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 94, Box 97–99, Box 102, Box 113–114)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 93, Box 405)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 97–99)
    - Photographs (Box 405)
  - Kingsmill, 1973
    Job location: Williamsburg, VA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 34)
  - Kirsten, Lincoln
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 34)
    - Drawings (Box 34)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 34)
  - Kliegl Bros. Lighting, 1947-1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 35)
    - Drawings (Box 35)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 35)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 35)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 35)
  - Kling, Dr. R.A.
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 35)
  - Kneses Tifereth Israel Temple, 1956
    Job location: Port Chester, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 35)
    - Drawings (Box 35)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 35)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 35)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 35)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 35, Box 384, Box 405)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 35)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 35)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 35)
    - Material Samples (Box 35)
  - Knoedler Gallery, 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 35, Box 412)
    - Drawings (Box 35)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 35)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 35)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 35)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 35)
    - Photographs (Box 35, Box 412)
    - Material Samples (Box 35)
  - Knoll Associates, 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 35)
  - Kootz Apartment, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 36)
    - Drawings (Box 36)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 36)
  - Kootz Gallery, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 36)
    - Drawings (Box 36)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 36)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 36)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 36)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 36)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 36)
    - Photographs (Box 36)
  - Koshland Apartment, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 36)
  - Kranz & Company
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 36)
  - Kreeger House, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 36)
  - La Fonda del Sol Restaurant, 1961
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 36–37, Box 405)
    - Drawings (Box 37)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 37)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 36–37, Box 385)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 37)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 37)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 37)
  - Lake Shore Drive Apartments, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 38)
    - Drawings (Box 38)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 38)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 38)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 38)
  - Lambert Apartment
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 38)
    - Drawings (Box 38)
  - LaPidus, Henry
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 38)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 38)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 38)
    - Photographs (Box 38)
  - Lee, Donna Studio, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 38)
  - Leigh, Douglas Office, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 38)
    - Drawings (Box 38)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 38)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 38)
  - Lescaze Office Building, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 38)
    - Drawings (Box 38)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 38)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 38)
  - Lever House, 1953
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 38, Box 412)
    - Drawings (Box 38)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 38)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 38)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 38)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 38)
  - Levitt, William J. Residence, 1965
    Job location: Millneck, Long Island, NY
    - Drawings (Box 337)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 337)
  - Lewis, Madison Residence, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 38)
  - Library -- Unidentified
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 38)
  - Library of Congress, James Madison Reading Room, 1971
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 38, Box 405)
    - Drawings (Box 38)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 405)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 38)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 38)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 38)
  - Life House, 1950-1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 39)
    - Drawings (Box 39)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 39)
  - Lighting Corporation of America
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 39)
  - Lighting and Electronics, Inc., 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 39)
    - Drawings (Box 39)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 39)
  - Lightolier, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 39)
    - Drawings (Box 39)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 39)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 39)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 39)
    - Photographs (Box 39)
  - Lillas, A.V., 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 39)
    - Drawings (Box 39)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 39)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 39)
  - Lincoln Center Plaza
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 359)
    - Drawings (Box 119, Box 270, Box 359)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 119, Box 270)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 270)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 119)
  - Lincoln Center, Edison Park and Lock Garage
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 359)
    - Drawings (Box 359)
  - Lincoln Center, Metropolitan Opera House, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 359)
    - Drawings (Box 173, Box 192, Box 204, Box 359, Box 362)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 192)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 173, Box 204, Box 362)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 173, Box 204)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 362)
  - Lincoln Center, New York Public Library
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 359)
    - Drawings (Box 170, Box 359)
  - Lincoln Center, New York State Theater [including Theatre of the Dance], 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 39, Box 359)
    - Drawings (Box 111–113, Box 171–172, Box 192, Box 202, Box 204, Box 221, Box 238, Box 359, Box 361–362, Box 365–366, Box 372)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 192, Box 366)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 192, Box 238, Box 362)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 111–112, Box 171, Box 202, Box 221, Box 238, Box 365, Box 390, Box 399)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 111–112, Box 171–172, Box 361, Box 365, Box 372, Box 390)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 111–112, Box 171–172)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 172)
  - Lincoln Center, Philharmonic Hall, 1966
    Collaborator: Harrison & Abramowitz
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 39, Box 358, Box 405)
    - Drawings (Box 39, Box 119, Box 192, Box 225, Box 245, Box 315, Box 358, Box 369)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 39, Box 192)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 39, Box 315, Box 389)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 39, Box 119, Box 315, Box 369)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 39, Box 225, Box 245, Box 315, Box 369)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 225, Box 245, Box 315)
  - Lincoln Center, Vivian Beaumont Repertory Theater, 1962
    Collaborator: Eero Saarinen, Skidmore Owings and Merrill
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 359)
    - Drawings (Box 157, Box 170, Box 201, Box 359, Box 363–364, Box 367, Box 371)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 157, Box 363, Box 367)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 157)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 157, Box 170, Box 201, Box 364, Box 367, Box 371)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 157, Box 170, Box 201, Box 371)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 170, Box 201)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 157)
  - Lincoln Center, Street Island
    - Unidentified Material (Box 359)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 359)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 359)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 359)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 359)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 359)
  - Lincolnshire Fabrics Ltd., 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 41)
    - Drawings (Box 41)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 41)
  - Lithographic Technical Foundation, Inc., 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 41)
  - Little Casino, 1946
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 41, Box 405)
  - Living House, 1950-1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 41)
    - Drawings (Box 41)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 41)
  - Living Magazine, 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 41)
    - Photographs (Box 41)
  - Living for Young Homemakers, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 41)
    - Drawings (Box 41)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 41)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 41)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 41)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 41)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 41)
  - Loeb Apartment, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 41)
  - Lovers Lane Methodist Church, 1967
    Job location: Dallas, TX
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 41)
    - Drawings (Box 41)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 41)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 41)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 41)
    - Photographs (Box 41)
  - Lucas Residence, 1953
    Job location: Nantucket, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
    - Drawings (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 42)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 42)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 42)
  - Mace, Borden Apartment, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
    - Drawings (Box 155, Box 237)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 155)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 155, Box 237)
  - MacNutt Electric Company, Inc., 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
  - Macy, Margaret (See Also: Margaret Macy Advertising Co.), 1950
  - R.H. Macy & Co., Inc., 1944
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
    - Drawings (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 42)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 42)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 42)
  - Maher, John F. Residence, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42, Box 386)
    - Drawings (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 42)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 42)
  - Maine Museum of American Painters, 1961
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
    - Drawings (Box 42, Box 169)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 42, Box 169)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 169)
  - Maisel, Arthur Residence
    Job location: Danbury, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
    - Drawings (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 42)
  - Majestic Apartments, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
  - Making New York Beautiful, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
  - Malino Apartment, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 42)
  - Manufacterer's Trust, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
    - Drawings (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 42)
  - Margaret Macy Advertising Co., 1950
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
    - Photographs (Box 42)
  - Market Street Opera House
    Job location: Delaware
    - Drawings (Box 199)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 199)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 199)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 199)
  - Marquette Fifth Building, 1974
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 405)
    - Photographs (Box 405)
  - Marvin Electric Manufacturing Company, 1966
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
  - Matthews, A. C. Residence
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 42)
  - Mayfair Hotel, 1950
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
    - Photographs (Box 42)
    - Material Samples (Box 95–96)
  - McFarland Clinic, 1960
    Job location: Ames, IO
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
    - Drawings (Box 42, Box 144)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 144)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 42)
  - McGinnis Office, 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
  - McIntosh Residence, 1955
    Job location: Bedford, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 42)
    - Drawings (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 42)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 42)
  - McLane Pavilion
    Job location: Millbrook, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
    - Drawings (Box 43)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 43)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 43)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 43)
  - Meadowbrook Hospital, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
  - Meah Shearin Temple, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
  - Meals, Mrs. Gordon, 1964
    Job location: Bedford, OH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
  - Mendelson, Dr. Curtis, 1953
    Job location: Sands Point, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
    - Photographs (Box 43)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art (MET)
    - Drawings (Box 120)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 120)
  - Middletown Manufacturing Company, 1956
    Job location: Middletown, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
    - Photographs (Box 43)
  - Miller Company
    Job location: Meridian, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
  - Herman Miller Textile Showroom, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
    - Drawings (Box 43)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 43)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 43)
  - Miller, Irwin Office, 1959
    Job location: Columbus, IN
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
    - Drawings (Box 43, Box 232)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 232)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 43)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 232)
  - Miller, Irwin Residence, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
    - Drawings (Box 43, Box 232)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 232)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 43)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 232)
    - Photographs (Box 43)
  - Paul Miller's Restaurant, 1954
    Job location: Manhasset, Long Island, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
    - Drawings (Box 43)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 43)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 43)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 43)
  - Milton Penthouse, 1946
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
    - Drawings (Box 43)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 43)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 43)
  - Milton Steinberg Memorial Center, 1952
    Job location: New York
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
    - Drawings (Box 43)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 43)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 43)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 43, Box 386)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 43)
  - MIT, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 43)
    - Drawings (Box 43, Box 124, Box 165, Box 246, Box 258, Box 281, Box 283, Box 289)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 43, Box 165)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 43)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 43, Box 165)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 43, Box 165)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 43, Box 165)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 124, Box 165, Box 246, Box 258, Box 262, Box 281, Box 283, Box 289)
    - Photographs (Box 281)
  - Moffit Apartment, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 44)
    - Drawings (Box 44)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 44)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 44)
  - Monaco Hotel, 1956
    Job location: Havana, Cuba
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 44)
    - Drawings (Box 44)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 44)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 44)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 44)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 44)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 44)
    - Drawings (Box 44)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 44)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 44)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 44)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 44)
    - Photographs (Box 44)
  - Morgan, Helen Apartment, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 44)
  - Morosani Residence
    Job location: Litchfield, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 44)
    - Drawings (Box 44)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 44)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 44)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 44)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 44)
    - Photographs (Box 44)
  - Morris, Herbert C. Residence, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 44)
    - Drawings (Box 44)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 44)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 44, Box 386)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 44, Box 386)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 44, Box 386)
  - Morris, William, 1950
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 44)
  - Morton, Mildred Apartment, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 45)
  - Motel on the Mountain (See also: Mount Hillburn Corporation), 1955
    Job location: Mount Hillburn, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 45)
    - Drawings (Box 45)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 45)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 45)